Where do I like to shop?
我喜欢去哪买东西?
Shopping is not my, my sport.
购物可不是我的...我的运动.
I, I am really not the guy to talk about shopping.
我,实在不是那个谈论购物的人.
I have a daughter who's 12.
我有个12岁的女儿,
and I found I enjoy shopping with her now.
我发现我现在喜欢跟她一起去买东西.
She's getting old enough.
她已经长大了.
We like similar things or we like totally opposite things,
我跟她有时喜欢相同的东西,有时截然相反,
but it's fun together.
但在一起很开心.
If we can find a mall that isn't as crowded,
如果可以找到不太拥挤的购物中心的话,
we'll go there,
我们会去,
but most of the time we go to neighborhood shops.
但大多数时候我们去社区商店.
Sometimes I like to shop.
我有时喜欢买东西.
Usually I prefer shopping from catalogs than going to the mall.
通常我更喜欢邮购, 而不是去购物中心,
because there are too many people.
因为那里人太多.
Who shops for my clothes?
谁给我买衣服?
Er, I shop for my own clothes.
Er,我自己买我自己的衣服.
I only shop when I need something.
我只在有需要时才去买东西.
I don't shop for pleasure.
我买东西不是为了休闲娱乐.
When we were younger, shopping was our recreation,
当我们年轻的时候, 买东西是我们的娱乐活动,
but now I do what I have to do and I don't do it any other time.
但现在我做我不得不做的事情, 而且我在其他时候不会去做它.
I'm a real bohemian, so we've been married for six years
我是个真正的波西米亚人,所以我们结婚六年了,
and I don't think I've bought any of my own clothes in six years, if that answers your question.
我想我还未给自己买过一件衣服在这六年中, 如果那回答了你的问题.
Automotive parts.
汽车零部件.
I'm big on automotive parts, sometimes.
我喜欢买汽车零部件, 有时.
The food shopping.
购买食品.
My wife does all the food shopping.
我妻子购买所有的食品.
I'm from Frankfurt, Germany, and we have a flea market every week, um, near the river.
我来自德国的法兰克福, 那儿每周都有跳蚤市场, um,在河边.
I like to buy there.
我喜欢到那里买东西.
Sometimes I go shopping even if I don't want to find anything myself.
有时我去逛商店, 即使我不想给自己买任何东西.
If a friend needs something, we just walk around and look at clothes
如果有个朋友需要买什么, 我们就会走来走去, 看看衣服
and you know, and talk and hang out, sometimes it is a social activity.
and you know, 聊天和呆在一起, 有时这是一种社交活动.
I prefer, er, family-owned small businesses
我更喜欢,er,家庭经营的小店,
'cause I think, um,
因为我认为,um,
there's a much more human quality involved in shopping in those stores.
在那种店买东西更富有人情味.
I think it's vital to, to keep those kind of community centers going.
我认为让这类社区中心继续运转非常重要.
I think the biggest mistake they've made in all around the world is they think that centralizing shopping has become something that makes sense.
我觉得全世界的人都犯了一个极大的错误, 他们认为集中购物相当明智.